vustudents.ning.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Virtual University of Pakistan

**We only collect anonymous information.  
**   
We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you. In other words, we do not collect information such as your name, address, phone number or email address.

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

**We may collect but do not share your location history.**   
To customize our service for you, we may collect and store your precise geographic location as part of your user profile. This data generally is not shared with others. We may ask for your consent on your first use of the service.

**You can not request to see your personal data in any condition.  
**   
You can sign into your account to see or delete any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, address, email or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see or delete this information.

**We may keep data indefinitely.  
**   
We may keep data indefinitely.

**We don't share your personal data with other companies.  
**   
We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies.

**No ad companies collect data through our service.  
**   
We do not allow advertising companies to collect data through our service for ad targeting.

**You can ask privacy questions.  
**   
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us:  
[[Contact us](http://vustudents.ning.com/opensocial/ningapps/show?appUrl=http%3A%2F%2Fapps.livewired.ws%2Fcontactus%2Findex.php%3Fning-app-status%3Dnetwork&owner=0lrhnllrdvalv)] OR [[EMAIL](mailto:m.tariqmalik@gmail.com)]

**Analytics providers access data on our behalf.  
**   
Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.

Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors.  

**We take steps to protect personal information  
**   
We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

**Special situations may require disclosure of your data.  
**   
To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so.

**Our full privacy policy includes more information.  
**   
This privacy policy was last updated on [11/11/2012]. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text. Please read our full privacy policy, which includes other important information.
